[Music]
by the
way please C the
subt app downlo Play Store or App Store
and currently in now
first time in you need to provide your
username and password Bally email
address and password and then
either after that
[Music]
make
payment and just
Insurance details recent payment post
may take two to three
[Music]
Visa
or and then
man life list of winners and provide
your policy
number bya
shoe Sal wallet to and Via online
backing China backi Metro
pet amount to pay is total and for
payment method is option available which
is and from here provide credit or debit
card details 16 digit card
number card and Master Card please
choose a relationship of card
holder to the payment terms and
conditions continue to payment
May viso so obviously it's a
[Music]
vis
number also you card verification number
or CV at email address by the way May
virtual
[Music]
card number expir date or valid through
date and
CB
submit number
dat add
[Music]
phone number link
may
[Music]
receive just to make
sure your payment transaction is
completed
screenshot as proof of
pment
continue and you've successfully
processed your payment may receive
enough text from Maya confirming this
exaction go to
P confirmation or anything about her
payment
instead for the
by reaching out to their support or
customer
service and very quick7
next